[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
No!
As a pair, we're unstoppable.
I can take down my father.
I can't watch that man win.
I won't let it happen.
He's not my real father.
Or how you made a girl go blind.
Everything.
You can't even properly operate
on your own.
It's okay.
What exactly are you so afraid of?
I can't believe you're still acting like
plastic surgery is taboo.
It can't be me. It has to be you!
Do you have a better plan?
If she says she wants to die,
you'll kill her? Have you lost your mind?
She's asking for one last chance
to be beautiful.
I'm a doctor.
I won't operate on someone who isn't sick.
Shit! I won't forgive you.
-Sorry?
-I'll say it again.
I will never forgive you.
He was the absolute worst.
What was Dad like?
DECONSTRUCTION
Fumi Numata, 33.
Passenger on a motorcycle accident.
-She needs to get to the OR.
-Don't worry.
Fumi? Fumi, talk to me. Are you okay?
We're gonna take care of you.
Just gonna move you. One, two, three.
She's on.
-We've got you.
-Where's Fumi?
-Checking for breaks.
-Miss, you're in good hands.
She needs a transfusion.
Let's get an IV in her.
-Setting up.
-Fumi!
I'm gonna be honest with you.
She sustained severe injuries.
Multiple fractures all over her body.
But she'll heal, right?
It's not like she's gonna die.
No, not likely.
Seeing as there's no visible trauma
to her brain or spinal cord,
with some time and treatments,
she'll make a full recovery
and get back to normal life.
With that said, things for her
won't be exactly the same as they were.
She suffered a strong impact to her face
when she hit the ground.
I need gauze.
There's also significant tissue loss.
Tissue loss?
The actual term is "facial disfigurement."
She will have permanent scarring
and changes to her appearance.
I need a new monitor as well.
Whatever the case,
she'll need to be hospitalized
as she recovers.
It would be best to inform her work
that she'll need medical leave.
I understand.
Accident?
It'll take her several months
to recover, I'm sure.
Congratulations, Governor.
You made it happen.
All thanks to you, Dr. Rin.
Please sit.
Where's, uh, that lady friend of yours?
She had an emergency to take care of.
I'm sorry. I'm afraid
it's just you and me today, Governor.
That sounds perfect.
It's all my fault.
I'm truly sorry
from… the bottom…
Honestly, I don't even know what to say.
Don't worry, okay?
Macky, you were injured as well, got it?
But Fumi…
She was saying how she felt better finally
after talking to Takeru.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
A prominent member of
the current governing party approached me.
And they invited me to have dinner
with Chairman Arata Tohyama.
So then,
what do you intend to do, Governor?
Well, I placed all my chips
on you, Dr. Rin,
and that turned out pretty good.
For this project,
I'm gonna need to go all out.
I want someone who represents the future.
Something so massive
needs a face people can trust.
I think my drinks will taste
extra good tonight.
I've been thinking of the chairman
and always wondered…
Why retire so early
if his intention was
to go up against you in the first place?
As far back as I can remember,
I don't believe there was ever
an official reason.
So as a special favor
in celebration of my reelection,
would you tell me?
All right, then,
but only as a special favor.
The full story is that
the chairman had chronic kidney disease
most of his life.
And he searched a long time for a donor.
Accident?
That's unfortunate.
But despite his patience,
his opportunity never came.
His condition got so bad
that he was on the verge
of kidney failure.
Then could that be
the reason that he went abroad was…
He ran out of time and patience,
and decided to use his connections
for a transplant abroad.
-Why don't you rest?
-Good idea.
You still love the chairman,
Dr. Rin, don't you?
Why the curiosity?
A transplant abroad could be in violation
of organ transplant laws.
It would have been easy for you
to expose the secret
during the conflict with the family,
but you chose not to.
I needed to keep my trump card
for the right moment.
No, no.
It was love. I know it.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Numata.
It's getting late.
Why don't we reschedule the meeting
for another day?
Are you coming over to my house?
Oh, it's Mommy.
Hey! Give me back my ball!
Ms. Numata.
Hmm.
That project right there, the diorama.
-Fumi made it during class.
-Hmm?
Seriously?
Honey?
It's beautiful.
Apparently, according to our art teacher,
she seems to have a natural talent.
Fumi may be what we call "gifted."
Gifted?
Mm.
Really?
And if it interests you two,
he said he would love to introduce her
to a top art school professor.
How does that sound?
That sounds amazing.
That's great.
Just the other day,
she said she wanted to be a doctor,
which is ridiculous.
I said, "Absolutely not,"
and to go into something less expensive.
Really? That's an incredible goal as well.
Fumi.
Why don't we get him to introduce you
to an art professor? Okay?
Changing the monitor now.
Ms. Numata? Can you hear me?
Get the doctor.
Right away.
Numata!
Can you hear me?
Numata?
Oh, thank goodness.
Take over for Dr. Numata? What?
It's an emergency.
Could you do it, please?
No. Not possible.
Please. You have to do it.
-Not a chance.
-Come on, Dr. Hikita.
It's a breach of contract.
The agreement is, I don't show my face.
It would only be temporary. Just until
we can find another doctor to replace you.
I can't.
I don't… I don't wanna talk
to patients anymore.
I don't wanna give someone the opportunity
to file another harassment complaint.
Huh.
Huh?
And what if you use this?
This way, you could stay anonymous.
No, no.
Find any promising candidates?
Yes, I found a few
from that headhunter's list
that was put together.
Something wrong?
Uh, Dr. Numata's file.
And this was put together by
Takashina?
Yeah, I think so.
Could you call him in, please?
Yes, no problem.
Excuse me, could you call in…
Hello, ma'am.
How are you today? Doing well?
Yes, thank you very much.
Take care of yourself, okay?
The change of seasons
can be quite tough on the body, all right?
Thank you very much.
Sorry to disturb you.
Mr. Konoike is here.
He'd like to have a word.
Oh. Here?
I was told
he's in the building right now, sir.
Hello, Governor.
Mr. Konoike, it's been a while, hasn't it?
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Well, it just so happens
that I was already meeting someone
around here.
In fact, I know
someone who would
appreciate meeting you, Governor.
Chairman.
Governor.
Congratulations on your reelection.
So, the chairman just put this together?
Correct, and things
such as the technical evaluation
were based on his opinion.
Understood. Thank you.
Is there something else?
Uh…
My apologies.
I have something I'd like to discuss.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Are you going to the chairman?
So it was you who leaked the information.
Well, seeing as you were
the chairman's lap dog,
this is unsurprising.
-Uh…
-No, it's fine.
Please, there's no need
to say anything at all.
Get out of my sight right now.
Ando, I'm guessing Dad asked you
to spy on me as well?
Excuse me? What do you mean "spy on"?
I was just worried, is all.
There's no need for you to worry about me.
That right?
I heard Dr. Numata, the new hire
you met at the press conference,
is already on leave.
Relax, okay? Stop being suspicious,
and just hear me out.
I'm actually more pissed off at Dr. Arata.
He keeps poaching my doctors, too,
and it's always with the same sales pitch
about how chain clinics are the worst.
Hey, Rin?
What do you say
we work together against him?
Are you ready, Fumi?
Do it.
Try not to be too surprised.
As a cosmetic surgeon,
what do you think of this?
Oh God.
Florida?
Plan is to open a clinic there next year.
And expand into South Korea and Singapore.
My idea was to go there myself
and be the director,
but I was thinking maybe
I could leave it to you.
Running the business here,
bending to the old guard in this country,
is exhausting, isn't it?
Look, Rin.
Leave him the Tohyama brand.
It's for the best.
-I'm not kidding. You should…
-No, sorry but…
I still have a…
a few things I need to do here.
I'm very sorry.
You should rest up
while the swelling goes down. Okay?
-Hey.
-Huh?
I'm… bored.
You're bored?
I can imagine.
Fortunately, that's not lethal, right?
Just take it easy.
In cosmetic surgery,
you call it "recovery time."
When you're healed up,
we'll talk to the plastic surgeon
about facial reconstruction options.
Yes.
Okay. Why don't we discuss terms, then?
Great.
Thank you. We'll talk again soon.
Oh, thanks.
Take a load off, huh?
I'm good.
I'm here, having a normal meal, aren't I?
I meant at the clinic.
Why not close it for a while?
Uh, I'm not sure I'm following?
You should wait for Dr. Numata to recover.
I told you, Dr. Numata wants to quit.
Yes, but you haven't accepted
her resignation yet, have you?
I know you can't find another doctor
that you could trust
as much as you trust her.
So, why don't you wait
until she's recovered, then?
But if…
I close the clinic now,
who do you think
that will end up benefiting?
So what if it does?
Sure, her connection to the chairman
was surprising.
But Dr. Numata went her whole life
not knowing who her father was,
and there's nothing you can do about it.
If you accept that, I know she'll stay.
No.
I just can't do that.
Oh, yeah?
And why is that?
You don't understand.
No, I'm afraid I don't get it.
Jeez. Are family connections and blood
really that important?
So what?
She's the chairman's daughter. Whatever.
It makes no difference to the patients
who come to the Tohyama Clinic for help.
Lily! You don't get it at all!
This isn't like you, Rin. Just talk to me.
I had no clue
you could be this insensitive.
Would you like to tell me
where you're going?
Don't be too long, okay?
My apologies
for visiting so late.
I want to talk about
your resignation letter.
I felt things were left in the air,
which isn't good
for you
or for me.
That's why tomorrow,
I'll begin the paperwork
for your resignation.
And as for the 200 million,
you don't need to pay me back.
I have caused you
more than enough pain already.
Going forward…
we'll go our separate ways…
and hope for the best.
MS. FUMI NUMATA
Back again?
I guess you should move in here.
Hi.
Huh?
O… Okura.
Look at you!
So, Dr. Tanuma, you used to be at
Musashino University Hospital, right?
Yeah, for around ten years.
The department chief was a real pain.
hat a relief that is.
I thought you might be a new doctor.
Mm, well, to be honest,
even doctors
with general medical experience
can actually be just as bad or worse.
Let's continue with the dissection.
Yes.
Yes. Good job.
No way!
You did a double-eyelid surgery on Takeru?
You got it.
Then, you're telling me
your last cosmetic surgery
was on your brother?
Yeah.
You're kidding?
I can't believe that! That's insane!
Insane?
So if that's the case,
would you be willing
to do my surgery next, then?
What?
Wh… Why?
But… I already quit.
No.
TOKYO GLOBAL BEAUTY HUB PROJECT
FIRST CONFERENCE DETAILS
Here we go!
This is seriously insane.
Hold on. Are you Takeru?
I'm happy we get
to finally meet each other.
Hey. Come in. I was just leaving.
Okura.
Thank you.
Oh no, don't worry about it.
Not how I wanted it to end either.
Well, just remember to enjoy
your well-deserved recovery time, okay?
Enjoy?
Of course.
It can't get any worse. You agree?
Mm. Yeah, sure.
While you recover,
try to believe that you're becoming
the best version of yourself.
If you try, even just for a moment,
you'll feel invincible.
Okay.
Be seeing ya.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
Want anything to drink?
Yeah.
Macky.
Macky?
How is he?
Oh, he's okay.
You probably shouldn't see him yet.
He seems to be struggling pretty hard.
-Hey, Takeru.
-Hmm?
I wanna see your eyes.
Not bad.
Thank you.
You'd rather hide them?
For now.
Hmm.
By the way,
what'll you do after being discharged?
Apparently, Dad needs a hostess
for the snack bar.
Uh…
Maybe I'll try art school.
Art school?
-Art school.
-Why?
Well, I'm
decent with my hands, right?
Yeah, sure.
When I was a kid…
my teacher said
I should look into an art school.
And so you applied?
Nah, I just checked it out.
Mm.
Our mother…
Mm?
…left before the visit ended.
What? Why?
I was just a grade school kid,
and she left me there.
Kinda crazy, huh?
I was devastated.
I wanted to get even.
Mom hated doctors, so I became one.
So that's why you became a doctor.
Exactly.
Jeez, Fumi.
Can you believe it?
That's how sad I was.
Thanks, by the way.
Huh?
For doing my surgery.
Of course.
RECOVERY TIME IS IMPORTANT FOR
A CHRYSALIS TO BREAK OUT OF ITS COCOON
AND TRANSFORM INTO A BUTTERFLY
INSIDE THE CHRYSALIS, THE LARVAL TISSUES
ARE COMPLETELY DECONSTRUCTED
Hurry up, Fumi!
We're gonna be late!
Apparently, this teacher is amazing.
I heard he even works on
designing churches in Spain.
What's wrong, Mom?
Mommy?
Hi.
-It's Tohyama.
-Ms. Tohyama.
Yes, I see. Right.
Excellent. I'll show you to your table.
Right over here.
Excuse us.
Well, for the cheek and jawbones,
we'll use plates made of titanium
and proceed with the nasal bone.
After, we'll monitor your progress.
Then, the next step, I believe,
would be to use a prosthesis
for nasal reconstruction.
F…
Uh, yes?
It's the same as cosmetic surgery.
Pardon me,
but we're hardly on the same level.
So what's next?
Well, this afternoon, I have
an intramedullary nailing operation.
Mm.
So anyway, Numata,
after being discharged,
why don't you come back to work here?
I spoke to the hospital director.
Don't worry.
As long as you're okay with it,
he's on board.
What do you know?
Now they want me back?
Uh, what?
You're not happy with that?
Mm.
Okay.
Take your time to think about it, Numata.
Please try not to take forever though.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-Hmm?
Hey.
Him?
Yo.
Hey.
This table right here.
-You kidding? Here?
-What?
This is where I was told to bring you.
-Why not by the stage?
-There he is.
Attention, please! Take your seats.
We're going to begin the conference.
Director.
-What the…
-Director.
Whoa! Director…
Are you…
Are you gonna take
everything away from me?
Well?
Go on!
Tell me why you're going this far!
I'm willing to do
whatever it takes
to protect what's important to me.
And what's important?
Is it Tohyama?
Is it more important than family?
Because you've completely lost it!
We all have something.
Something we don't wanna have taken
from us.
Something important we don't wanna lose.
My apologies.
Sorry, everyone. Let's carry on.
All right, everybody. Please simmer down.
Let's begin the conference!
Take your seats, please.
Please, everyone.
We ask for your cooperation.
If we can all settle down,
we have a short amount of time.
We kindly ask for your cooperation.
Hey.
You know…
this was probably for the best.
How could you even think that?
Look.
Honestly…
it gave me a chance to think
about my life.
Oh, yeah?
Hmm.
Hey.
Hold on a sec.
-Get closer.
-Uh, yeah, yeah. Just gimme a second.
Mm.
Ah, there you are.
Hey, Macky.
You can't work at the snack bar forever.
You know that, right?
Hmm.
Okay, but…
Hmm?
What if…
What if I keep working
at the snack bar forever?
Do whatever you want.
Thank you.
Stop! Stop!
Please, stop.
Stop. Please, stop, stop.
Stop it! Please, stop.
Stop it!
Director?
Pardon me, but…
It's Ms. Konoike. She, um…
She fell hard on her face.
Call a damn ambulance, then!
-She's already on her way here.
-This is a cosmetic surgery clinic!
But she's already on her way.
-Let go of me! No!
-Please sit down.
-Calm down. Please sit. Right here.
-Let go! Let…
I need you to sit in the chair.
-Ms. Konoike, please calm down.
-No!
-Help me! I need help now! It hurts.
-Please. Sara.
It hurts so much! It hurts!
-See, Dr. Rin is here.
-Take it easy!
Calm down!
I'm gonna call an ambulance.
You need to go to the hospital
to be examined, okay?
No, you can't do that to me!
We can't do X-rays here.
You promised to take care of me forever!
Sara! Listen!
I'm only doing this
for your own good, all right?
I'm gonna call your family, okay?
But you promised.
You promised.
You gave me your word you wouldn't.
Please, Rin.
I don't care.
I need you to treat me here.
Rin.
Director.
I'll do it. Don't worry.
I'll handle her surgery.
I'll…
I'll do it.
The first conference
for the Tokyo Global Beauty Hub Project
was held today.
Ambassador Mr. Arata Tohyama,
former director
of the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic,
was among those in attendance.
The atmosphere at the Tokyo…
Excuse me.
I'll be taking you
to the operating room now.
-Scalpel.
-Here.
-Ms. Fumi Numata is ready.
-Okay.
-Shall we begin?
-Yes.
She should go to the ER.
-It'll be fine.
-But we can't treat her here.
Director.
We can't do this.
The work of the successor
of the Hand of God.
It's okay.
I can do this.
All right, let's move her.
Ms. Konoike mentioned a promise.
What did she mean by that?
Truth is that she…
She's never told her family
that she lost…
sight cause of my mistake.
Huh?
And it looks like she never told them
about having plastic surgery either.
Oh God. I…
I'm such a damn idiot.
When she… told me
she wanted to keep it from her…
from her family…
I figured
I'd use the promise to hide my mistake.
At least that's what I thought.
I really only care about
looking out for myself.
And that's why
I destroyed the clinic like I did.
I'm going to close
Tohyama Clinic.
Take it easy.
You're still under anesthesia.
You've gone through a lot.
Dr. Numata…
it's very clear…
that you're my daughter.
Of course,
I don't expect you to understand it all.
But…
I'm not sure how much time I have left.
That surgery I had a while back
didn't exactly work.
So I need to be precious about my time.
Le…
Let go. Let go.
Only now I realize
what's actually important.
It's blood.
How could…
How could I
have been so foolish?
Someone of my own blood…
was there all along, and yet…
Could you be the one…
to carry on our bloodline?
Cheers.
I still remember
the first time I assisted you in surgery.
I can say this now.
I saw your genius.
I had never seen a facelift performed
that quickly.
The result was perfection.
In that moment, I knew that
"The Hand of God" exists,
and I get to work with someone incredible.
I take back closing the clinic.
Huh?
Just joking.
I'm not a genius. You know that?
The other doctors would throw a fit
if they heard you say that.
I'm dead serious.
Ever since…
Ever since I was a kid,
I screwed up everything.
And 'cause of that,
I've always had insecurities.
It must have been
when I started junior high.
I went on a TV show.
It was my dad's regular show.
"Trust in the Hand of God."
So then, while filming,
suddenly, my dad,
he announced I was to be his successor.
On public TV,
in front of a massive studio audience.
In any case, my dad was just…
Well, I think
he was just putting on a show.
Though as a child, it was…
it was an incredible feeling.
I…
worked hard to be what I am.
Well, then,
your hard work really paid off.
That's not it.
All I had was the patience
to put in the time and effort.
I'm pretty sure
my dad saw through it a long time ago.
He knew I wasn't really
the next "Hand of God."
So that means
the second Hand of God will be Rin?
Well, I might be biased,
but she's hardworking,
and I'm sure she'll be a great doctor.
A worthy successor to the Tohyama name.
And Rin?
Any thoughts on what your dad just said?
I'll try my best.
She accepts! How exciting.
I look forward to what she does
in the future.
This week's Beauty Revolution
is brought to you live
straight from
the Tokyo University of Fine Arts campus,
where the school's festival
is in full swing!
Well then, Doctor. Would you, please?
Trust in The Hand of God.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much, everyone!
Thank you.
And don't forget
to watch the broadcast later!
-Mommy!
-Thank you very much!
Mommy, where are you going?
Mommy!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Lily.
I always end up hurting you.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
You seem to have quite a vested interest
in the Tohyama name.
Do you mind telling us
what brought you to the decision
to let it go?
Well, a father knows
when they're no match for their daughters.
I figured any more conflict
wouldn't be beneficial for either of us,
so I decided to withdraw.
Are you planning to go ahead
with the new clinic opening?
Well, on that subject,
I'll have to reconsider
the clinic's location,
so as not to cause
any more issues with the Tohyama Clinic.
I will be renaming it, after all.
Have there been discussions
with your daughter on all this?
Director.
Did I talk to her?
I'll leave it at that.
-Oh.
-Mm.
Wait, you're not… coming back?
No.
So you… won't come back
even though the hospital director said
you could?
No, thanks.
-You're sure?
-Yes.
Jeez, what a waste.
Can you imagine
how much we're going to lose?
And you're sure
you want to give up the name too?
Dr. Komiya.
So then, you and I will work together?
There's just one… condition.
What do you mean?
Tohyama.
Give it up.
Let her have the name.
That's… what I want.
Chairman.
What do you mean there's been a delay
with opening the clinic?
I've decided
to make some changes at the clinic.
A new location with a new director.
Don't worry.
I'll update you when necessary.
But, Chairman Arata,
I came here
just so I can work by your side.
I deserve an explanation.
Who'd you choose as the new director?
Unfortunately, if working for me
is what you came for,
I'll have to ask you to leave.
What?
Those who want an easy ride
on someone else's coattails,
I have no use for.
All right.
I know whatever I say doesn't matter.
It won't change your mind, anyways.
Let me know
when you've decided what's next.
Hold on.
Hmm? What's up?
Just one more thing.
Just one more thing?
It…
has to do with my face.
You're quitting?
Yeah, today…
will be my final day ever.
But didn't the chairman
give up the Tohyama name?
No, I won't let this happen.
Or did you forget what you did, Rin?
I haven't forgotten.
I could never forget that.
I'll forever…
carry that mistake with me
for the rest of my life.
But today…
Well,
I think that it's the best time
for us to end this arrangement.
It's for the best.
If we don't do this now,
we'll be stuck in this loop forever.
It'll be painful at first, I know,
but I need to make this all public.
Does this mean you're gonna abandon me?
Not at all.
I promise I will never abandon you again.
Even though
today is my last day in practice,
I'll be right there,
and I'm gonna make sure
that you continue to receive
your treatments just as before.
After all, we've known
each other for a long time.
So…
let's do this together, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
Really, Rin?
Yeah.
It's gonna be all right.
Well, you called it, Director.
The chairman is, in fact,
quite the sneaky bastard, after all.
What are you saying?
Numata.
The chairman made her the director
of his new clinic.
Dropping the Tohyama name
and canceling the Tokyo clinic opening
were all a part of Numata's demands.
Can you believe that?
Takeru?
The other day, I told you, right?
That it's best we go our separate ways.
I'm here today…
as a patient.
Director.
I'm asking…
for you to fix my face.
And why me, then?
This isn't personal.
I just…
need you to be the one to fix it.
I looked down on cosmetic surgery.
So this must be a bit of a shock to you.
But then…
working here, I've…
I've met so many patients…
which got me thinking,
"Maybe…
it's my turn to try to change myself."
I always depended on others.
Yet, my own family had no value to me.
I want you to do my surgery.
I want to change.
Director.
Please.
I'm asking for another chance.
For new wings to fly.
I also need…
new wings so I can fly.
Fumi, I need that as well.
That's why I accepted your resignation…
and made the decision to close the clinic.
I want more than anything
to move to the next stage as well.
I cannot perform…
your surgery.
I'm very sorry.
I understand.
Of course.
Thank you…
Director.
In other news,
this week will mark the closing
of Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
A clinic with a long history,
dating back to the early Heisei era.
Perhaps having Tokyo
select highly skilled clinics
and awarding them stars?
Similar to Michelin stars?
Yes, exactly.
Huh. Great idea.
That would make things much clearer
to the overseas clients.
Very clever.
The sudden closure
has brought on criticism
and shock from patients.
As a way to ease the transition,
Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic
has announced it will handle all transfers
for patients that had made reservations
to the MDC Minatoku Beauty Clinic.
Oh, hi Sara.
Wasn't expecting you. Come on in.
I'd like to talk to Grandfather.
Oh.
Takeru.
Hmm?
I'm saying goodbye to my old face.
-Does that make you sad?
-Huh?
Let's take a photo
to immortalize this moment
before the surgery.
Immortalize what?
This?
-Huh?
-Why not?
I'll get Dad and the others.
That's not necessary.
What's there to immortalize?
Apparently, you delayed your flight back.
I just figured I would
take it easy over there for a while.
So then,
if you have no further issues,
I'm going to be announcing the opening
of the new Florida clinic
as early as next week.
I'm okay, thanks.
If you have ideas, you let me know.
The Florida clinic will be yours to run
how you like, Rin.
I fully trust your intuition.
Let's see, red and black bookkeeping.
Thank you for waiting.
…flight 62, bound for Los Angeles,
departing at 11:05, is now ready…
NANAMI TODOROKI
HAVE A GREAT TRIP!
…first-class passengers,
top-tier status members…
The time's come.
Mm.
My face is in your hands now.
-Have a safe trip, sir.
-Thank you.
Attention, please,
priority boarding is now in progress
for JFL flight 62…
What's up?
…departing at 11:05,
Rin!
TAKERU SENT ME THIS.
SOUNDS LIKE THE OPERATION IS STARTING NOW.
I… I can't.
I have to go back right away.
What's going on? You feeling all right?
I keep running away, even though…
I knew all along what…
actually matters.
All right, I'll be placing a mask on you.
Slow breaths, okay?
Beginning anesthesia.
You're gonna start feeling sleepy.
You can't go in!
-Huh? Hey!
-Stop! You can't go in!
Dr. Tohyama?
She asked me…
She asked me to perform her surgery.
She wanted me to be the one
to fix her face.
I'm sorry, but it's too late for that.
I'm begging you!
It's the truth.
I'm telling you, she asked me to do it.
I'm the only one who can do it.
To give her new wings.
Hey, Dr. Rui here!
How is everybody out there doing?
Someone special will be joining us
on today's Cosmetic Surgery
for Beginners lesson.
None other than
MBC's very own idol, Moenon!
Hey!
-It's me, Moenon.
-Adorable.
We actually knew each other before MBC.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, we did.
And that was years
before you had plastic surgery, which was…
I was in the fifth grade.
So around two years ago.
-Mm.
-Yeah, that's right.
-Two years ago.
-Oh wow.
-Two years goes fast.
-It does.
So that means
you're in junior high, right?
Yeah, it's my first year of junior high.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Wait, so you decided?
Hmm, I have.
I talked with my mom yesterday.
What'd she say?
She said it was okay
to go for a consultation.
I have to talk to her first
before deciding what to do next.
Ah, so she might just say no, then.
Hmm, basketball's kinda cool, but…
Yeah, but I think I'll go with orchestra.
-You sure?
-Yeah. So what'll you do?
-I prefer music, so…
-Hmm.
-I probably won't pick sports.
-What?
-Definitely do sports.
-You're right!
-I'm home.
-Hey, Takeru.
Oh, hi, Mikana.
Come in.
She's actually here for a consultation.
Seriously?
You need your parents' consent though.
It's okay
if it's just a consultation, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, here you go.
Fill out this form.
Thanks for coming in today.
Thank you.
-See you again next week, all right?
-Right. Next week.
-Thank you.
-Take care.
-Thank you, bye!
-Hey, Takeru.
-Hey, Maki.
And your email goes here.
Yeah, yeah. Just like that.
Perfect. Don't forget dot com.
Oh, don't worry. We have an opening now…
Oh.
Come in, please.
Sorry… to interrupt.
It's been a while.
It has been.
Here you go.
I figured
you'd be working for the chairman.
You closed Tohyama Clinic, so why would I?
I didn't owe Tohyama anything anymore.
Still, though.
Wasn't expecting you
to open a cosmetic surgery clinic.
I gotta earn a living.
Besides, it's become
a bit of a family business.
I can tell.
Saw you on Insta.
You did a lot of traveling
to all sorts of countries,
lots of good food.
Thought to myself,
"She's having a great time."
-You mind if I look?
-Mm.
You're gorgeous.
You look perfect for me.
Says the Hand of God herself.
Are you finished with… cosmetic clinics?
I'm finished.
It's too much pain to build a new clinic
from the ground up.
Yeah, isn't that the truth, huh?
Though…
I could see myself buying a small clinic
and taking over as the director.
Oh.
I see.
People who always solve everything
with money work on a different level.
Hmm?
Two hundred million work?